Guide to the Joe Negri Collection, 1930-2014 CAM.JNC.2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Original Compositions, I.
  - Beck's Charter Oaks Shows, 3.
    - "They Feed the Cuckoos at 9 O'clock", 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1249)
    - "Yes, We're Going Bananas!", 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1250)
    - "Whatever Happened to Desdamona Fink?" (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1251)
      Missing.
    - "Desdamona Fink & Oh Where, Oh Where Has Samantha Schnook Gone", April 27, 1963 (Box 28, Reel 163)
      1 reel.
      Original Inscription Songs from Desdamona Fink & Oh Where, Oh Where, has Samantha Schnook Gone Recorded April 27, 1963 - Pgh. 26, PA *Judy Knaiz *Bob McCully *Joe Negri Side One: I Feel Great - Judy K. Desdamona Fink - Bob McC & Joe N. Conformity - Trio Mr. Right - Judy Give Love a Chance - Joe Bachelor's Lament - Bob Just Gotta Do It - Judy Wonderful World of Crime - Joe & Bob Charlie - Judy Misty Valley - Joe
      Side Two: Airline Stewardess White House Shuttle Wonder If Victim of Love Found my Love Woman of Stone I Like the Girls
    - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 259, Item 259)
      Photocopy of list of titles (shows or song in shows?) and dates. Holograph.
    - J&B (Box 5, Folder 259, Item 260)
      Typed list of song titles with performers in parentheses.
  - Film Music, 4.
    - Air Pollution Film Theme I, February 20, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 1832-1836, Item 1832)
      Air Pollution film.
      Also inscribed: TAE Clients Party & Industrial Shows
    - Air Pollution Theme II, February 20, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 1832-1836, Item 1833)
    - III Polution (Box 21, Folder 1832-1836, Item 1834)
    - Pollution (Box 21, Folder 1832-1836, Item 1836)
    - Film Score Alcoa History of Aluminum (ALCOA), March 27, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 1841, Item 1841)
      Holograph score. 6 pages. 2 copies.
    - Melancolia Theme (Box 21, Folder 1814-1819, Item 1814)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 pages. 2 copies.
      Contents orignally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription:
      Amazonas Score 8/14/67 Joe Negri
    - Amazones I (Box 21, Folder 1814-1819, Item 1815)
    - Film sound list (Box 21, Folder 1814-1819, Item 1816)
    - Amazones II (Box 21, Folder 1814-1819, Item 1817)
    - Peracu (Box 21, Folder 1814-1819, Item 1819)
    - Bossa Verde, October 20, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1821)
    - Chant (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1822)
    - Main Theme (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1823)
    - Opening (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1824)
    - Africa (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1825)
    - Show listing (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1830)
    - Music (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1831)
      Holograph manuscript. Listing of Show music. 2 pages on notebook paper.
    - [untitled] (Box 21, Folder 1821-1831A, Item 1831A)
      Holograph music manuscript. 1 page.
    - Minor Theme Consol Film (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1796)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 3 pages.
      contents original enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription:
      Consol Film
    - General Ind. Theme (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1797)
    - Consol Theme piano (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1787)
    - Consolidated Coal Co. Opening I horns (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1799)
    - #III horns (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1800)
    - #IV Horns, tenor trumpet (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1801)
    - Consol Themes horns (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1802)
    - Consol. Coal Co. I Opening bass (Box 20, Folder 1796-1803, Item 1803)
    - #III Bass (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A)
    - #V Bass (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1805)
    - #VI Bass (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1806)
    - Consol Theme Piano (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1807)
    - Opt. #2 Bass (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1808)
    - Opt. #2 Horns (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1809)
    - Opt. #2 horns (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1809)
    - Consol Theme piano (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1810)
    - Minor Theme Consol Film piano (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1811)
    - General Ind. Theme II (Box 20, Folder 1804-1811A, Item 1811A)
    - 6 min. (Box 20, Folder 1811B.1-1811B.2, Item 1811B.1)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 12 pages. 2 copies.
    - 6 min. Guitar (Box 20, Folder 1811B.1-1811B.2, Item 1811B.2)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscripts. 10 pages.
    - 6 min. Piano (Box 20, Folder 1811B.3-1811B.4, Item 1811B.3)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 12 pages.
    - 6 min. Drums (Box 20, Folder 1811B.3-1811B.4, Item 1811B.4)
    - 2 1/2 min (Box 20, Folder 1811B.3-1811B.4, Item 1811C)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 pages. 4 copies.
    - Minor theme Consol Film piano (Box 20, Folder 1811B.3-1811B.4, Item 1811D)
      Photocopy of holography manuscript. 3 pages.
    - Heart of the Law Theme opening (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838)
      Holograph manuscript. 5 pages.
      contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription:
      WTAE Films Heart of the law
    - Heart of the Law Rock Theme (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.1)
    - Blues II Jail Scene (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.2)
    - Heart of Law 2nd Theme Poverty (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.3)
    - Heart of Law Opening Theme guitar (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.4)
    - Rick Theme guitar (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.5)
    - Jail Scene guitar (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.6)
    - Heart of Law Opening Theme Electric Bass (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.7)
    - Heart of Law Rock Theme Eletric Bass (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.8)
    - Jail Scene electric bass (Box 21, Folder 1838, Item 1838.9)
    - Heart of Law (opening theme) piano (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.3)
    - Rock Theme (piano) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.31)
    - Jail Scene piano (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.32)
    - Heart of Law theme opening (trumpet & horn) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.4)
    - Heart of Law Theme II (Povery) horn (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.41)
    - Blues II Jail Scene (horn) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.42)
    - Rock Theme (horn) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.43)
    - Heart of Law Theme Opening flute, April 20, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.5)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 page.
    - Heart of Law Theme II (Povery) flute (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.51)
    - Jail Scene (flute) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.52)
    - Rock Theme (flute) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.53)
    - Opening Theme (drums) (Box 21, Folder 1838 folder 2, Item 1838.6)
    - Our Native Quarters 1st Theme (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839)
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Our Native Quarter Heart of Law
    - Native Quarter guitar transition (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.01)
    - Victor Herbert big (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.02)
    - After blues - guitar trans - Bb (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.03)
    - Our Native Quarter Theme 1 Bass (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.1)
    - Native Qt Trans. & Melodic Theme (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.11)
    - After Toyland bass (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.12)
    - Native Quarter Theme I (piano & guitar) (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.2)
    - Native Qt. Trans & melodic theme piano (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.21)
    - After Babes in Toyland piano (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.22)
    - Our Native Quarter Theme I trumpet (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.3)
    - Native Quarter Trans. & Mel. Theme trumpet (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.31)
    - After Babes in Toyland trumpet (Box 21, Folder 1839, Item 1839.32)
    - Dance for Devi (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1783)
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: WTAE TV Special - Shalom Music Score - Joe Negri Lead & Rhythm Parts Recorded - May 15th, 1970 W.R.S. Studios
    - "Dance for Devi" guitar (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1783.1)
    - Shalom Aleichem (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1784)
    - Shalom (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1784.1)
    - Jerusalem bass, guitar and drums (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1785)
    - Jerusalem flute (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1785.1)
    - Jerusalem cello (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1785.2)
    - Going Back flute and cello (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1786)
    - Going Back bass, guitar & drums (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1786.1)
    - Delila (Box 10, Folder 1783-1786A, Item 1786A)
    - Oak Tree (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795)
    - Oak Tree bass & drum (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1787.1)
    - Shalom (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1788)
    - Jerusalem theme (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1789)
    - Shibolim (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1790)
    - Debka Habir (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1791)
    - Hadoodaim (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1791.1)
    - Hebrew Theme (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1792)
    - Hebrew Theme bass (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1792.1)
    - Religious Theme bass (Box 10, Folder 1787-1795, Item 1793)
    - Tin Whistle (WQED) (Box 10, Folder 1761, Item 1761)
      Holograph manuscript. 3 pages. 2 copies.
      Material for Recording Guitar w/ Love After today Spring in Manhattan Tin Whistle Lazy Day Round Midnight Harlequin Watch What Happens Django Serenata Felicidad A Time for Love
      Serenata - concert band - arrangement
    - To Give a Hand (Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel) (Box 18, Folder 1684-1685)
    - Wheeling Steel Opening (Box 22, Folder 1869, Item 1869)
      Holograph score. 6 pages.
      Wheeling Steel Film
    - Wheeling Steel bass (Box 22, Folder 1869, Item 1869.1)
    - Wheeling Steel guitar (Box 22, Folder 1869, Item 1869.2)
    - Wheeling voice (Box 22, Folder 1869, Item 1869.3)
    - Wheeling (Box 22, Folder 1869, Item 1869.4)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 8 pages. Missing pages 1 & 2.
    - Ventroux Film (State of West Virginia) (Box 22, Folder 1878)
    - W. Virginia Film Opening (Box 16, Folder 1527-1533, Item 1527)
      Holograph manuscript. 2 pages. 3 copies.
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Ventroux Film - W. Virginia Film.
    - Fire Sequence (Box 16, Folder 1527-1533, Item 1528)
    - Aftermath (Box 16, Folder 1527-1533, Item 1530)
    - Vintroux (sic) Film flute (Box 16, Folder 1527-1533, Item 1533)
      Holograph manuscript. 6 pages.
    - Vintroux - Film [sic] flute (Box 17, Folder 1591-1594, Item 1594)
    - "Ventroux Film (State of West Virginia)" (Box 28, Reel 1878)
      1 reel marked handle with care.
      Original Inscription: Scotch 201 Vintroux [sic] Music for Joe Negri.
    - X-100 Film, April 2, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 1840, Item 1840)
      Holograph manuscript. 3 pages. 5 copies.
  - Early Compositions/College Material, 5.
    - "Buy That Extra Bond" (first Composition), 1942 (Box 3, Folder 161, Item 161)
    - Dialogue for Violin & Piano, 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 144-145, Item 144)
      photocopy of holography manuscript. 9 pages.
      Contents originally enclosed in folder with the following inscription:
      Original composition for Violin & Piano Composed by Joe Negri 1952@ Car. Mellon Univ.
    - Dialogue for Violin and Piano (Box 2, Folder 144-145, Item 145)
    - Dialogue for Violin & Piano (Box 2, Folder 146, Item 146)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 9 pages.
    - Dialogue for Violin and Piano (Box 3, Folder 150, Item 150)
      holograph manuscript. 12 pages.
    - "Minuetto", 1951 (Box 2, Folder 148-149, Item 148)
    - "Minuetto" (Box 2, Folder 148-149, Item 149)
      holograph manuscript. 3 pages. 2 copies.
    - "Beat 'em Bucs" (Pittsburgh Pirates Fight Song), Sept. 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7-11, Item 11)
      Lead Sheet for Beat 'em Bucs. Holograph manuscript. Revised edition.
    - "Chorale Prelude: Mein Jesu' Was fur Seelenweh" (Box 3, Folder 203, Item 203)
    - Chorale Prelude letter, October 21, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 203, Item 203.1)
      letter from "Roland" to Joe re manuscript.
    - Class Notes, Carnegie Tech (Box 4, Folder 229)
      contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Harmony Studies Carnegie Mellon Nicolai Lopatnicot 1950-1952
      Folder enclosed in manila envelope with the follow inscription:
      Original compositions for Carnegie Tech by Joe Negri
  - River City Brass Band, 6.
    - "Pittsburgh on Parade", September 15, 1991 (Box 27, Cassette 2)
      High Bias Dolby cassette tape. 5 pieces by Joe.
    - "Voyager in Four Parts" (Box 26, Item 1233)
      Two spiral notebooks of photocopied holograph scores, one for Guitar, Flute & Vibes; One for Electric guitar, flute & Vibes.
    - Newspaper clippings about "The Voyage in Four Parts"
      - "Joe Negri takes Center Stage This Weekend in the River City Brass Band", October 11, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1234-1236, Item 1234)
        1 newspaper clipping.
      - "RCBB Gusts Propel Negri on 'Voyage,'", October 12, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1234-1236, Item 1235)
        Newspaper clipping. Daily news.
      - "RCBB to Debut Negri's 'Voyage,'", October 7, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1234-1236, Item 1236)
        McKeesport Daily News newspaper clipping.
    - Songs Performed with the River City Brass Band
      - "A Train" (Box 12, Folder 1158-1160, Item 1158)
        Holograph score. Solo guitar arr. by Joe Campus. 3 pages.
      - "Satin Doll" (Box 12, Folder 1158-1160, Item 1159)
        Holograph score. Solo guitar arr by Joe Campus. 2 pages.
      - "Misty" (Box 12, Folder 1158-1160, Item 1160)
        holograph manuscript. arr by J. Campus. 3 pages.
  - Poetry Forums, 7.
    - 1981 Poetry Forum: "America Made in Paris"
      - Bass
        Contents enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription:
        Poetry forum 1981 America Made in Paris Bass Book
        - "Signing in the Air" (Box 10, Folder 900-912, Item 900, Item 901)
        - "Next Time You Were There" (Box 10, Folder 900-912, Item 901)
          handwritten notes.
        - "Jelly Roll" (Box 10, Folder 902)
          Photocopy of holograph manuscripts.
        - "Nuages" (Box 10, Folder 902, Other 902)
        - "Napoleon's" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 904)
          Photocopy of typed lyrics. 2 pages.
        - "Waiting for Zero" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 905)
          Photocopy of printed lyrics. 2 pages.
        - "Naima" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 906)
        - "Django" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 907)
        - "Django's Castle" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 908)
        - "All Colors End in Black" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 909)
        - Notes for #10 and #111 (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 910)
          photocopy of handwritten notes.
        - "Understand the Highway, Understand the Country" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 911)
          Photocopy of Typed lyrics. 3 pages.
        - "The Next Time You Were There" (Box 10, Folder 902, Item 912)
        - "I Will Say Goodbye" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 913)
        - "Windows" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 914)
        - "The Vigil" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 915)
          Photocopy of typed lyrics. 5 pages.
        - "Sexes" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 916)
        - "Some Words for President Wilson" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 917)
        - "White Silence" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 918)
        - "Elegy for the First Life" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 919)
        - "The Long Passion" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 920)
        - "Words for President Wilson" [notes] (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 921)
          handwritten notes. 1 page.
        - "Au Privave" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 922)
        - "Goodbye Pork Pie Hat" (Box 11, Folder 913-923, Item 923)
          Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 page.
      - Guitar, 1981
        - "Walkin' Toward the Sun" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 924)
          photocopy of holograph manuscript. 8 pages. two copies.
          Poetry Forum 1981 America Made in Paris Guitar Book -
        - LaRoche College America Made in Paris (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 925)
          handwritten notes on yellow paper of show order.
        - "Next Time You Were There" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 925A)
        - "Signing in the Air" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 926)
          Photocopy of printed lyrics. 3 pages.
        - "The Virgil" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 927)
        - "Afternoon in Paris" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 928)
        - "Impressions" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 929)
        - "Sexes" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 930)
        - "Napoleon's" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 931)
        - "Jelly Roll" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 932)
        - "White Silence" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 933)
          Photocopy of printed lyrics.
        - "Nuages" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 934)
        - "All Colors End in Black" (Box 11, Folder 924-935, Item 935)
          Photocopy of typed lyrics. 4 pages.
        - "Django's Castle" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 936)
          Photograph of holograph manuscript.
        - "#11 - The only Comedy" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 936A)
        - "The Only Comedy" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 937)
          photocopy of typed lyrics. 5 pages.
        - "Understand the Highway, Understand the Country" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 938)
        - "Au Privave" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 939)
        - "Windows" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 940)
          Photocopy of holograph manuscript. Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription:
        - "Waiting for Zero" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 941)
        - "An America Made in Paris" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 942)
          photocopy of handwritten show order. 2 pages, stapled.
        - "Elegy for the First Life" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 943)
          Photocopy of printed lyrics. 1 page.
        - "The Long Passion" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 944)
        - "Nuages" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 945)
        - "Jelly Roll" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 946)
        - "Jelly Roll" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 947)
          Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 page. 2 copies.
        - "Naima" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 948)
        - "Naima" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 948.1)
          Holograph manuscript. 2 copies.
        - "Windows" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 949)
        - "I Will Say Goodbye" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 950)
        - "W.W.I. Montage" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 951)
        - "#11 - the Only Comedy" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 951A)
          Handwritten notes. 3 pages.
        - "Some Words for President Wilson" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 952)
        - "Goodbye Pork Pie Hat" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 953)
        - "I Will Say Goodbye" (Box 11, Folder 936-954, Item 954)
      - Percussion, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 879-899)
        - "Jelly Roll" (Box 10, Folder 879-891, Item 879)
          Contents enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription:
          Poetry Forum - 1981 "America Made in Paris" Piano Book [circled] Percussion
        - "Nuages" (Box 10, Item 880)
        - "The Long Passion" (Box 10, Item 881)
        - "Windows" (Box 10, Item 882)
        - "Signing the Air" (Box 10, Item 883)
        - "The Vigil" (Box 10, Item 884)
        - "Sexes" (Box 10, Item 885)
        - "Napoleon's" (Box 10, Item 886)
        - "White Silence" (Box 10, Item 887)
        - "Elegy for the First Life" (Box 10, Item 888)
        - "All Colors End in Black" (Box 10, Item 889)
        - "The Only Comedy" (Box 10, Item 890)
        - "Understand the Highway, Understand the Country" (Box 10, Item 891)
          photocopy of typed lyrics. 3 pages.
        - "The Next Time You Were There" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 892)
        - "Some Words for President Wilson" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 893)
          Photocopy of typed lyrics. four pages.
        - "Waiting for Zero" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 894)
        - "The Long Passion" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 895)
          Photocopy of typed lyrics. 6 pages.
        - "#1 - Next time You Were There" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 896)
          Handwritten notes.
        - "An America Made in Paris Run Down" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 897)
          Handwritten notes. 1 page.
        - "Nuages" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 898)
          photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 page
        - "Goodbye Pork Pie Hat" (Box 10, Folder 892-899, Item 899)
    - Sam Hazo International Poetry Forum: "Traveling without a Ticket"
      - "Traveling without a Ticket" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 955)
        Handwritten show list.
        Contents enclosed in brown folder with the following inscription:
        Traveling without a Ticket [Sam Hazo] Int. Poetry Forum Concert - Feb - 6,7,9, 1983 Joe Negri's address is also inscribed
      - "The Next Time You Were There" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 956)
        Photocopy of typed poem. 2 pages.
      - "Florence by Proxy" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 957)
      - "My Roosevelt Coupe" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 958)
        photocopy of printed poem. 1 page.
      - "I Will Say Goodbye" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 959)
        Photocopy of holography manuscript. 1 page.
      - "The First and Only Sailing" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 960)
        Photocopy of printed poem. 2 pages. Contents enclosed in brown folder with the following inscription:
      - "Splitting" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 961)
        photocopy of printed poem. 2 pages.
      - "To a Bicyclist in France" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 962)
        Photocopy of printed poem. 2 pages.
      - "Flying Down the Dream" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 963)
      - "May You Run out of gas near Punxsutawney" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 964)
        photocopy of printed poem. Two pages.
      - "No Echo in Judea" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 965)
        Photocopy of printed poem. 1 page.
      - "Living's How we Die and Vice Versa" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 966)
      - "Silence Spoken Here" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 967)
        Typed poem. 2 pages.
      - "Long Distance Isn't" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 968)
      - "Carol of a Father" (Box 11, Folder 955-969, Item 969)
      - "Celebration" Guitar Part (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 970)
        holograph manuscript. Guitar Part. Bass Drums Eric Kloss.
        Contents enclosed in brown folder with the following inscription: Traveling without a ticket [Sam Hazo] Int. Poetry Forum concert - Feb. 6, 7, 9 1983
        Joe Negri's address is also inscribed.
      - "Celebration" Guitar Part (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 971)
        Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 copies.
      - "Concierto De Aranjuez" (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 972)
      - "The Answer is Yes" (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 973)
        Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 pages. 2 copies. By Jim Hall
      - "Nardis" (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 974)
        photocopy of holograph manuscript. 1 page. 4 copies. by Miles Davis.
      - "Gentle is My Lover", December, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 975)
        Photocopy of holograph manuscript. By E. Kloss. 1 page. 3 copies.
      - "Foot Prints" and "Black Nile" (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 976)
        Holograph Manuscript. By Wayne Shorter. Verso side has holograph manuscript of Black Nile by Wayne Shorter.
      - "Walk Soft" (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 977)
        Photocopy of holograph manuscript of Jim Hall.
      - "Seascape", 1982 (Box 11, Folder 970-978, Item 978)
        photocopy of holograph manuscript by Eric Kloss. 1 page.
      - "Theme from Spartacus" (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Folder 979)
      - "Theme from Spartacus" bass (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 980)
      - "Traveling without a ticket" flier (Box 11, Folder 979-990, Item 981)
        flier for "Traveling without a ticket."